{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991905937","data":{"timestamp":" 947991905937"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991912590","data":{"timestamp":" 947991912589"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991920922","data":{"timestamp":" 947991920922"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991928801","data":{"timestamp":" 947991928801"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991939148","data":{"timestamp":" 947991939148"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991945660","data":{"timestamp":" 947991945660"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991952019","data":{"timestamp":" 947991952019"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991959015","data":{"timestamp":" 947991959015"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991971901","data":{"timestamp":" 947991971901"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991981526","data":{"timestamp":" 947991981526"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991990654","data":{"timestamp":" 947991990654"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991990877","data":{"timestamp":" 947991990877"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991991841","data":{"timestamp":" 947991991841"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991993114","data":{"timestamp":" 947991993114"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991996039","data":{"timestamp":" 947991996039"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991996883","data":{"timestamp":" 947991996883"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991997196","data":{"timestamp":" 947991997196"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947991998429","data":{"timestamp":" 947991998429"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992001954","data":{"timestamp":" 947992001954"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992002937","data":{"timestamp":" 947992002937"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992003190","data":{"timestamp":" 947992003190"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992004133","data":{"timestamp":" 947992004133"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992006942","data":{"timestamp":" 947992006942"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992007975","data":{"timestamp":" 947992007975"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992008448","data":{"timestamp":" 947992008448"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992012959","data":{"timestamp":" 947992012959"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992013020","data":{"timestamp":" 947992013020"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992017677","data":{"timestamp":" 947992017677"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" e32f2595-21a4-40b2-a026-375d3a5433a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992046304","data":{"timestamp":" 947992046304"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_383_832-998-383"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 383"," userResponse":" 383"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992058671","data":{"timestamp":" 947992058671"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 244"," userResponse":" 244"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992073879","data":{"timestamp":" 947992073879"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 259"," userResponse":" 259"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992088340","data":{"timestamp":" 947992088340"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 625"," userResponse":" 625"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992100896","data":{"timestamp":" 947992100896"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_112_461-128-112"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 112"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992115189","data":{"timestamp":" 947992115188"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_422_420-422-684"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 422"," userResponse":" 422"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992130561","data":{"timestamp":" 947992130561"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_272_272-699-619"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 272"," userResponse":" 272"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992146002","data":{"timestamp":" 947992146002"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 414"," userResponse":" 414"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992161409","data":{"timestamp":" 947992161409"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_411_607-109-411"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 411"," userResponse":" 411"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992179327","data":{"timestamp":" 947992179327"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 74"," userResponse":" 74"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992186792","data":{"timestamp":" 947992186792"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992201100","data":{"timestamp":" 947992201099"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992206745","data":{"timestamp":" 947992206744"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992211804","data":{"timestamp":" 947992211803"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992222642","data":{"timestamp":" 947992222642"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992234711","data":{"timestamp":" 947992234711"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992241471","data":{"timestamp":" 947992241471"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_060437"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}